<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Safeguard for Pokemon GO</string>
    <string name="launcher_app_name">Safeguard</string>

    <!--Menu Item Strings-->
    <string name="action_settings">About</string>
    <string name="action_donate">Donate</string>

    <!--Dialogs and Dialog Buttons-->
    <string name="error_dialog_title">Error!</string>
    <string name="error_dialog">Seems like you don\'t have Pokemon GO installed! </string>
    <string name="welcome_trainer">Welcome, Trainer! You have Pokemon GO installed and
    you\'re all good to "GO" and stay safe as well :D</string>
    <string name="weclometitle">Installed!</string>
    <string name="warning_title">Careful!</string>
    <string name="warning">Be careful, Trainer! Remember to look up and stay aware of your surroundings!</string>
    <string name="button_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="dialog_donate_title">Donate</string>
    <string name="dialog_donate">Wanna donate to help me create more apps like this?</string>
    <string name="pre_thanks">Thank you for any donation. I am a single developer with little income, so
    this can be used to help pay for my school and help create more cool apps :)</string>
    <string name="post_thanks">Thanks a lot! ^_^ ♥</string>
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="about">Safeguard is an app made by Marlon Jones to keep players of Pokemon GO safer by giving constant
    notifications and dialogs every 15 minutes to ensure the safety of players.</string>
    <string name="dialog_test">This is a test of the dialog! You\'ll see this when you first boot up the game and if you have
    Android 4.4 Kit-Kat, you\'ll see this every 15 minutes on screen</string>
    <string name="notification_test_error">You don\'t have Android 5.0 or above! Because of this, the Heads-Up notifications will not work.
    You will instead see dialogs.</string>

    <!--Cards and other text-->
    <string name="card_entry">Welcome to Safeguard! This very simple app\'s goal is to keep you safe by giving you notifications or dialogs
    every 15 minutes while playing Pokemon GO to keep you safe and to remind you to stay aware of your surroundings. Even though
    no single app or software can prevent all accidents while playing Pokemon GO or any other Augmented Reality app, the goal is
    to at least help keep people safer while doing so. </string>
    <string name="button_on">Turn services ON</string>
    <string name="button_off">Turn services OFF</string>
    <string name="test">Test Dialog</string>
    <string name="test_2">Test Notification</string>
    <string name="check">Open Pokemon GO</string>

    <!--Notifications and SnackBars-->
    <string name="notification_test">This is a test of the Heads-Up notification! You will see this every 15 minutes when playing Pokemon GO!</string>
    <string name="bar_on">Service is on!</string>
    <string name="bar_off">Service is off!</string>
    <string name="bar_undo">UNDO</string>
</resources>
